Mateusz Darmochwal

Front-End Developer & Graphic Designer













WORK EXPERIENCE

MD / Freelance

Create my own brand from foundation. Making websites based on Bootstrap and Wordpress technologies, using HTML, CSS, jQuery. In addition, graphic creations, branding and the creation of marketing materials for printing.

Brake Bros LTD / Warehouse Operative

Picking products in accordance with the order on the invoice system. Assisting managers with running the reports, carrying out health and safety checks. Stock checking, receiving the deliveries, checking for damaged items, packing orders, keeping paperwork up to date, making sure all stock is labelled and stored correctly frames.

March 2014 - May 2016 Webera / Co-Owner

Co-founder of Marketing agency - Managing four members of staff -Service and Customer acquisition. Building websites in Word press and coding in HTML5 / CSS3. Creating graphic design: logos, business cards, leaflets, posters etc. Running social media, content marketing

Dec 2014 - May 2015

Gravity Personnel / Agency Employee

Work in chillers warehouse at Waitrose. Picking products in accordance with the orders on the invoice. Reporting to managers - Loading lorries

July 2010 - March 2014

Emporium Group sp. z o.o. / Managing Director, CEO and founder

Transformation of business sole proprietorship of a limited company. Management of the company, strategic decision making, business development. Support for large business customers, offering financial products. Recruitment, training, motivating the sales department. Marketing planning, creation and implementation.

Emporium Finance / Business Owner

Creation of advisory loan for individuals and business customers. Working closely with banks and insurance brokers

Krajowy Rejestr Długów BIG S.A. / Sales Specialist

Active sales via phone, presenting company's offers. Post-sales customer service. Reporting to managers

Eurobank SA / Advisor Sales

Branch service in the form of instalments program, Delivery and promotion of financial products. Implementation of sales plans. Preparing reports for the Management

AIG Bank Polska SA (Santander Bank) / Junior Specialist

Instalment Sales - Branch services presentations in an electronic shop. Delivery and promotion of financial products. Implementation of sales plans - Creation of reports for managers

LATEST PROJECTS

szpital-trzebnica.pl

St. Jadwiga's Hospital in Trzebnica

HTML CSS WORDPRESS LOGOTYPE SCRUM

Remote work in a team of 5 using the scrum methodology. I created a logotype according to the patterns and guidelines for the vector file. I have designed geographic maps of each hospital floor with a map of directions. Also created the layout of the subpages

mattdarm.github.io

MD - Portfolio Website

HTML CSS BOOTSTRAP BRANDING

I designed and developed a minimal and responsive portfolio using HTML5, CSS3, jQuery and Bootstrap. I created a logo (branding) and mockups for my graphic designes.

adwokat.stambulski.pl

Michal Stambulski - counselor

HTML CSS WORDPRESS DESIGN Responsive website based on WordPress platform. I was responsible of designing the individual subpages and creating icons based on the client's guidelines.

marmalmarmic.com

Marmal & Marmic LTD

HTML CSS WORDPRESS BRANDING

I designed the whole brand from the scratch. The logotype was created according to the client's design and concept. Responsive page has been implemented on cms Wordpress.

PERSONAL STATEMENT

A highly motivated and well organized professional with three years of experience in web development and graphic design. Hard worker with proven track record of both, high spec roles as well as the most humble jobs in case of such need. Tremendous attention to detail while making sure that all duties are carried out to meet the highest standards within deadlines. Formerly owner of a marketing agency, now a freelancer focusing on developing career and gaining more skills. Interested in opportunities as Front-End Web Developer.

LANGUAGES

HTML5 CSS3

JavaScript

LIBRARIES / FRAMEWORKS / CMS

WordPress Bootstrap **jQuery**



familiar / proficient / skilled

•••••

••000000

TOOLS / APPS

Chrome Developer Tools Git / GitHub LESS Node.js Adobe Photoshop Pixelmato Atom / Sublime



DEVELOPMENT

Responsive Web Design W3C Standards & Accessibility Cross browser compatibility Progressive enhancement

PROJECT MANAGEMENT

Remote working Scrum Trello Asana Basecamp

SOFT SKILLS









ACHIEVEMENTS



St. Jadwiga's Hospital in Trzebnica

I took part of a 3+ months massive project in a team of 5 for a highly regarded European hospital in Poland specializing in hand microsurgery.



Dartech Service

After 5 months from the positioning kick-off, I amended a few keylog phrases for the top10 in google search engine.



Emporium Group

Achievement of financial turnover for 2012 at the level of more than 1 million zloty - a significant figure for the local microeconomy.

CERTYFICATIONS

Online course certificate "Web Designer" - strefakursow.pl Certyficate of "Trustworthy Company" for Emporium

EDUCATION

Sept 2003 - April 2006 ne 2016 - present

High School no. 9 Wroclaw, Class - Human Sciences Free Code Camp (online course) - Front-End Web Developer StrefaKursow.pl (online course) - Web Designer, Javascript Developer

LANGUAGES

Polish - Fluent

English - Intermediate